<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SWE-DIU</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="chairmanmsg">\n \u00A0 \u00A0 \u00A0 Welcome to Daffodil International University.
        We are in the era of globalization and the globalization in the sense of economy, education
        and otheraspects. The system is changing and merging with the information superhighway.
        The demand of education has been changing with the aspect of global economy and adoption
        of new technology.\n\n
        \u00A0 \u00A0 \u00A0 DIU is very concerned about the change of technology and the
        requirement of human resources in the global market and in view of that change different
        programs have been introduced and will be introduced in the coming days of DIU. We are also
        concerned about the human resource demand for the local industry. Adaptation of new programs
        will enrich the human resource of Bangladesh and DIUs one of the mottos is to convert people
        to human resources and build them for the local as well as overseas employment. \n\n
        \u00A0 \u00A0 \u00A0 Innovations in technology and communications have enabled the
        educational sector to expand its realm in providing education to a wider range of students
        in extensive areas. Daffodil International University is dedicated to utilizing the latest
        technologies in its efforts to bring the best possible education to students all over the
        country. We provide them with the services and opportunities necessary to enable them to
        complete their respective educational programs successfully.\n\n
        \u00A0 \u00A0 \u00A0 DIU believes in quality and genuine education and also aware of the
        phenomenon of genuine and quality education. Daffodil International University ensures
        experienced and rich faculties, updated curricula and modern environment. Faculties take a
        genuine interest in educational development of the students and because of the comfortable
        size of DIU, it is able to provide students with genuine education and intellectual
        opportunities. In addition, our curricula provide numerous academic and career options for
        ones path to professionalism. Besides the academic opportunities, at DIU students will also
        find a host of extracurricular activities to round out their collegiate experience and
        enrich their resume.\n\n
        \u00A0 \u00A0 \u00A0 The current time demand is to elevate a university to international
        standard. The standard has many dimensions: they include the materials which are studied;
        the courses which are offered; the students who are taught; the faculties who teach them
        and undertake research; the places where teaching takes place; the environment and context
        within which teaching and research are undertaken. Above all, internationalization is a
        state of mind.\n\n

        \u00A0 \u00A0 \u00A0 Keeping the eyes on students career, DIU has introduced short courses
        like SUN, CISCO, Microsoft Certification courses beside the undergraduate and Masters
        programs. DIU is conscious how the students could enter into their professional life with
        a good background and enrich their professional life within short time.\n\n

        \u00A0 \u00A0 \u00A0 I wish every success of all students in their educational and
        professional pursuits.</string>
    <string name="headmsg">\n\u00A0 \u00A0 \u00A0 It gives me pride and pleasure to introduce the
        Department Software Engineering Department (SWE), Daffodil International University (DIU).
        As you read this, I hope that you will realize that our
        department recognizes the role the degree of Software Engineering plays in modern day of
        human life and activity.\n\n
        \n\u00A0 \u00A0 \u00A0 Department of SWE started its journey with only 15 students. Today
        the student number stands at 500. The department offers BSc and MSc programs in software
        engineering. This department has been working with a vision of developing vibrant software
        and IT professionals to meet twenty first century challenges.  In today’s competitive work
        environment, earning an advance academic degree is the first step to a highly successful
        career and if the degree could lead it one of the highest paid jobs in the world then it
        just gives the career a few steps head start.\n\n
        \n\u00A0 \u00A0 \u00A0 Our beloved country is full for young people who have the necessary
        intellectual potential and patriotism to bring about enormous changes to everything
        concerning the economic welfare of its people. We in SWE are here to help students burgeon
        their potential into complete professional person.\n\n
        \n\u00A0 \u00A0 \u00A0 It is really difficult to make a decision when comes to higher studies.
        To make the right decision at right time dose matter a lot with respect to fulfillment of
        your desired goal.  SWE invites you of the realm of knowledge and sharing an experience
        with a difference.\n\n
        \n\u00A0 \u00A0 \u00A0 I appreciate your interest in our department and programs and would encourage
        you to stay in touch with us if you have any questions or suggestions.
    </string>
    <string name="devinfo">Tanvir Ahmed\nID : 131-35-379\n</string>
    <string name="devinfo2">Abudullah Al Muhaimin\nID : 131-35-406\n</string>

    <string name="vrstyhsitory">\n\n\u00A0\u00A0\u00A0 \u00A0\u00A0 \u00A0\u00A0 \u00A0\u00A0\u00A0
    Daffodil International University is one of the finest university in Bangladesh.
    It is well known for its quality and performance.Daffodil International University believes on
        change with modern era with information and technology. It is the first IT based university
        in Bangladesh.
        \n\n\u00A0\u00A0\u00A0 \u00A0\u00A0 \u00A0\u00A0 \u00A0\u00A0\u00A0 The honorable Chairman
        of DIU Md. Sabur Khan starts this university with a dream and hope of educating the students
        using IT.
        \n\n\u00A0\u00A0\u00A0 \u00A0\u00A0 \u00A0\u00A0 \u00A0\u00A0\u00A0 As a result the
        university has been started with 67 students registering in the first batch and more than
        17,000 students have been enrolled till date.
    </string>
    <string name="contactvrsty">Contact\n\nAdmission Information and Counseling Office
    \nDaffodil Tower- 5, Dhanmondi, Dhaka-1207
    \nPhone: 8129348, 8129402, 8130864, 8129177, Ext: 328
    \nFax: 88-02-9131947
    \nshila@daffodilvarsity.edu.bd</string>
    <string name="deptabout">\n\n\u00A0\u00A0\u00A0 \u00A0\u00A0 \u00A0\u00A0 \u00A0\u00A0\u00A0The
        department of Software Engineering offers the program of B.Sc. in Software Engineering. The
        program is designed to produce skilled manpower for global IT market in order to satisfy the
        growing demands of software professionals throughout the world. It provides the students an
        opportunity to gain a vast knowledge about the overall Software Engineering process as well
        as Computer Programming, Computer Systems Engineering, Telecommunication Engineering and
        Electronics Engineering. The central goal is to create knowledgeable, efficient and skilled
        software engineering graduates so that they are able to make themselves competent to work on
        not only with the Software Industries in home country but also with any giant technological
        organization of the world.</string>
    <string name="deptcontact">Contact\n\nDaffodil Tower-04 (Main Campus)
        \n102/1, (4th floor), Shukrabad, Mirpur Road, Dhanmondi, Dhaka-1207
        \nPhone: 9138234-5, 9136694, 9116774
        \nFax: +88-02-9131947 </string>
</resources>
